(Leonard:)- Look, I'm no expert in women...
- I'll say.
(Leonard:)Not necessary when
someone's trying to help you.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, it's the alcohol talking.
Go on.
(Leonard:)Sometimes with women
you wanna listen to what upsets them...
...and show them that you
can grow and change.
(Sheldon:)Nuts to that. What else you got?
(Leonard:)I don't know what to tell you.
Buy her something.
(Sheldon:)How does that work?
(Leonard:)Well, you skip over any attempt
to repair your emotional connection...
(Leonard:)...and you win back her affection
with an empty financial gesture.
(Sheldon:)Well, that approach has
Sheldon Cooper written all over it.
- Glad I could help.
- It's appreciated.
If you manage to find a woman again,
I'll be glad to return the favor.